Hello everyone
I'm Brother Xin
a blogger striving to deliver substantial content
Today, we're going to create a film-like video like this
Let's first take a look at the final result
OK, does the effect look pretty good?
First of all, you don't need to memorize the video prompts
Just grasp the general idea
I will send you the detailed prompts privately.
Just give it a Triple Combo and follow with a comment to get it.
First, we need to generate a static image
a good static image
can establish a good reference for us in the early stages
especially for the first segment of the video
The prompt here is
I mainly focused on describing the characteristics of the dragon
a description of the character's features was provided
The most crucial aspect is to highlight the contrast between the dragon and the character.
convey a sense of colossal scale and oppressive presence
This is very helpful for us to produce high-quality
Filmic visuals are very helpful
Here, I have two suggestions for everyone.
First, it's essential to enhance the quality requirements for preliminary images.
Because the way we create videos now
the approach has undergone significant changes
our current video can have image references
the prompts can be written very simply
Moreover, on the basis of these high-quality images
we can elevate the quality of the video to the next level
The second tip is to follow a certain logic when writing keywords.
For example, we first need to describe the
what is the general atmosphere in the frame
and what content is present in the scene
what our character looks like
If there are other creatures
what do they look like
Finally, we need to describe the environment and the language of the lens again.
Because essentially we are using a virtual camera to capture a virtual scene
So, the language of this shot is extremely important.
OK, let me emphasize this again
This prompt will be quite lengthy
So I'll privately send you all the prompt phrases I've used
as long as you like, share, and comment with a follow
Creating videos is not easy
and look forward to your little support
Alright, let's continue
Now that we have this picture
we can now create our first shot
Our prompt is very simple
just add this image to the reference images
write close-up to medium shot
The dragon glanced at the character
hinting that he can ride on it
This is what I mentioned earlier
Our creative approach has undergone significant changes
If our reference image is relatively accurate
and it does not infringe on any rights
without any restricted content
we can use very simple prompts
to create a very impressive image
Next, let's move on to the second technique
generate two images
use these two images as the start frame and end frame
generate using the first and last frame approach
Here, I not only used the first and last frames
and imposed textual constraints on our shot content
The character rides on the dragon's neck
the dragon briefly gathered its strength
soared into the sky
At the moment of takeoff, it generated a massive shockwave
Then it soared freely and swiftly through the air
Cut to a close-up of the character with an extremely satisfying expression
this is our, the end frame
Here, I'll also provide the generation prompt for this image to everyone.
This is the result we generated.
Because this is my second demonstration
So it's different from the result I generated the first time
Everyone is also in the process of multiple generations
find the specific clips you need
and then edit it into our final shot
As you can see, the generated effect is also very good
That concludes our tutorial section.
Now I'd like to share some of my recent reflections on AI
The first is some characteristics of the AI era
The first is the information explosion
Finding good content has become more difficult
The second point is that the baseline quality of content has been raised.
mainly because replication has become too easy recently
especially the rapid replication of some viral hits
The Ultraman vs. Monster series that was quite popular a few days ago
Whenever a viral video appears
a large number of homogeneous contents immediately emerge
Moreover, on this basis
Everyone will give this viral hit an upgrade
from the initial Ultraman fighting monsters
to Ultraman fighting cats
to a child hitting a cat
to kids fighting kids
I feel that this kind of rapid replication leads to rapid aesthetic fatigue
Fatigue makes me exhausted from watching videos every day.
But it is precisely because of this aesthetic
The fatigue has led to an overwhelming urge to create recently
It's like feeling nauseous from eating too much good food.
I just really want to say it
This feeling is also caused by the excessively rapid update speed of the tools.
And I used to think Blender and UE
The update speed is already very fast
but now with the emergence of AI
I find their updates are still too slow
I even feel like the things I'm talking about
it might become obsolete the week after next
will become outdated
OK, now let me talk about what I'm currently doing
and why I'm doing this, uh
The first thing is to try to keep everyone from getting too anxious
Because every day, I'm bombarded with numerous viewpoints.
and I try my best to provide you with some of the latest
the latest News and development trends
and I hope everyone clicks on Me
the video can at least teach you something
At the very least, the content I update
content that I personally find quite valuable
I won't hold anything back
because it's unnecessary
As I just mentioned
Today's content might become outdated by next week
I think everyone mainly watches my
the video is just for fun
It's okay to brag a bit, I hope my videos can at least make everyone feel calm while watching
a state of being less anxious
I also hope that my content can be helpful to everyone
Finally, let me share with you some recent
some content about Seedance
and some trending videos
First, here's some rather surreal news at the beginning of 2026
Now the international internet has started reverse bypassing
using Hong Kong nodes to access Doubao
A good product going global can make foreigners learn Chinese in reverse
This is quite surreal
Here are some of the most popular videos recently
One is this 5-minute short film directed by Jia Zhangke
This content is quite lengthy
You can go and check it out
It feels quite good.
I just smoothed out some wrinkles
I smoothed out some wrinkles for you, and also shed 10 pounds effortlessly.
unable to repay
the imitation in ghost stories
OK, next up is this video
It now has many views on foreign platforms
over 10 million views
And I see there's a translated video available on Bilibili
You can go and check it out
I think the character consistency is maintained very well
Let's take a look at some clips together, Sophia today
You can see some great special effects in this part.
my way
I
You can look this up later and check it out yourself
You should be able to find it by searching for '10 million views' on Bilibili.
seedance with tens of millions of views
OK, and there's also this Speed watching himself
a scene of oneself transforming into Luffy
I think it's also quite fun
got me feeling so right
And then there's this utterly ridiculous clip of making dumplings during New Year
Ah, the way these dumplings are wrapped, even Kratos is getting impatient
Hahaha, ah
This is how the dumplings are made, ok, that's all for today's video.
See you next time